<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Socio-Traffic</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="emailid">Emailid</string>
    <string name="log_in_form">Log In form</string>
    <string name="email_id">Email id</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="allready_an_user_click_here">Allready an user?(Click here)</string>
    <string name="about">
        SocioTraffic is developed as a group project under the CDAC-Noida
        institution in guidance of Ms. Rosy Verma.Joint efforts of Shreyash Singh, Uditi Jain,
        Jyoti Rai and Dinesh Kumar have made an attempt to ease traffic struck life of people in
        Delhi.Socio-Traffic works to create a hassle-free drive time for the users of app by empowering
        them with traffic updates in their area through socializing on the app via posts from other
        users.We at Socio traffic aim to exempt out users the troublesome traffic jam and help them
        into a smooth and on time ride.We understand the value of time but more valuable is life.
        Our users can actively help the ones in need by contacting nearest hospitals in their area
        by the contact details yhat we have provided.
    </string>
    <string name="text1">Q.What should I do if I am stopped by traffic police?\n Ans: You can do either of the following things:\n 1. Pay-up: Pay the compounding amount against a receipt or\n 2. Contest: Surrender a document (like driving license) against a challan receipt and attend the court on a given date. In the court, after contesting the case, you will be either: i) acquitted or ii) fined. </string>

    <string name="text2">Q. What documents should a driver carry when driving?\n Ans: A driver should carry following documents when driving:\n 1. Driving License\n 2. Registration certificate\n 3. Taxation Certificate\n 4. P.U.C Certificate\n 5. Insurance Certificate.\n 6. Fitness Certificate and permit. </string>

    <string name="text3">Q.What are duties of a driver in case of an accident?\n Ans: The driver duties include:\n 1. Arrange some medical help.\n 2. Inform police. </string>

    <string name="text4">Q. How Can I edit my profile?\n Ans: You could simply go to “Profile” in “Menu” panel and click on “Edit” to make changes and “Save” after done. </string>

    <string name="text5">Q. What does reported in my post mean?\n Ans: If any content is offensive and another user of the app finds it in appropriate, they can report it. </string>

    <string name="text6">Q. What Action will be taken if my post is reported?\n Ans: If your post has been reported 5 times the post will be automatically deleted from the timeline. </string>

    <string name="text7">Q. Why is there a list of Hospitals in the app?\n Ans: In case you witness any accident, these listed hospitals are the nearest in your current area that you can contact for first aid. </string>

    <string name="text8">Q. What can I do in case my vehicle has been towed?\n Ans: Contact the nearest Traffic Circle. You will be required to pay compounding amount for improper parking plus towing away charges depending upon your vehicle type. </string>

</resources>
